okay this should be working
uh hopefully it is okay cool
so today we are going to talk about
oh well hello i&#39;m the ranches and today
we&#39;re going to be talking about
pairwise disjoint on how to be able to
solve a problem
that asks you to rewrite an expression
or not expression uh grammar as para
pairwise disjoint
so say we have this grammar
here this is just one the rules and
grammar this is our target rule that we
need to pay attention to
seven uh q
i this is non-terminal by the way i just
didn&#39;t put the little things brackets
around it
uh 9 q
then 7q
q8 okay
yeah that&#39;ll work that&#39;ll work so
uh we could just zoom in and zoom out
just a tiny bit
so i could fit everything in
and then sorry let me come back and
do the pen and then
uh sorry about that
seven q seven nine seven
q seven
nine okay so this is what we&#39;ve got
right
so we have z is seven q
is seven then non-terminal q the nine
the non-terminal q
or seven the non-terminal q then eighth
and
or seven then non-terminal q then seven
the nine
right and the paralyzed joint test says
that for every
part of this for every or statement
so for every or statement which is this
the first value must be different
now as you can see this fails that test
because the first value
is not different actually the first
value is in fact the same on all of them
we have to find a way to change that and
the best way to do it here at least in
our situation
is to come down here and recognize that
this
repeats this pattern right here repeats
itself in each rule so then we could
create a rule for that right we could
say okay
uh we could say z is equal to
seven q right so we r rewrite z
as 7q then z prime
right and then we can define z prime
as 9 q
or 8
or seven nine
and now if you go back and look and
check to see whether the first
uh part the first each
section has the the first part of each
section
is the same value you see that
in this z rule the only value is seven
so it is it is unique right
here in each or part
we change we see that the first value
here is nine the first one is
eight and first one here is seven so
that&#39;s basically how you do it now if
you kind of if you want to
verify that you&#39;re what you&#39;re saying is
correct think about how you could
use these rules to create the original
rule right and the way you could do that
is that you could say okay well if i
want to create the original rule
i can substitute the z uh prime
for 9q right and i get this rule i
substitute that z prime
for eight q uh i substitute
z prime for eight i get this rule
substitute it for seven nine
i get this right here so this should all
kind of hopefully make a little more
sense to you guys
thanks for watching