okay imagine on a first date instead of
you just nervous yapping yap yap yap
nervous yapping about yourself probably
imagine instead of that you had the
option to present your best qualities on
a PowerPoint presentation to the other
party well that&#39;s what this video is
today let&#39;s get into
[Applause]
[Music]
it hi I&#39;m Justine in a man I definitely
looking for someone who has a little bit
of confidence and definitely very
intelligent a PowerPoint is really going
to let me you should be looking for a
dude with good PowerPoint skills too I
feel like that&#39;s pretty essential not
only for this but just for real life how
often do you have a bunch of real good
info but you&#39;re like I need a I need a
fun way to present this that happens
pretty often in life sometimes it&#39;s good
to have a you know a partner that can
kind of show you the ropes see how these
guys think about themselves I hope to
see some I&#39;m not the best at PowerPoint
you know which sucks cuz I got a lot of
[ __ ] proprietary info up here you
know I&#39;d love to share it but they just
no elegant way to do so sometimes what
am I going to do speak it no that
wouldn&#39;t do it justice you know who can
have fun and make me
laugh I think we&#39;re going to start with
Antonio all right let&#39;s go
Antonio he&#39;s like how you doing my name
is Antonio hi he&#39;s like first slide name
oh Antonio I covered that already sorry
already covered that next slide oh I
duplicated that by accident okay name
Antonio okay next slide a [ __ ] how many
times did I duplicate this [ __ ]
slide you got the name right you you&#39;re
you&#39;re clear on that Antonio okay cool
just making sure you got that so I put
together a uh uh presentation for you
about why you should date me and as you
can see it&#39;s it&#39;s really a simple
decision oh I&#39;m down to earth and this
is a [ __ ] I&#39;m sorry for interrupting
so much but this is a hilarious concept
truly it really is like what would you
put on yours like there&#39;s a bunch of
[ __ ] that&#39;s not true you just all these
qualities that you don&#39;t that you don&#39;t
have spontaneous and a creative uh
former athlete so I&#39;m I&#39;m pretty
competitive so three pictures that
represent me um these are both music
related this is actually from my last
show I did a show with Soulja Boy so
that was pretty cool I grew up listening
to him uh this is from a music video I
Shot then this is from college were you
a quarterback no no I&#39;m way too short
for that uh running back okay I&#39;ll play
running back yeah what are you writing
down there what the [ __ ] was that
running back okay I&#39;ll play running back
yeah what the [ __ ] are you writing down
n too short for that okay um
uh
short short dumbass disgusting short man
cool got it thanks I&#39;d be so nervous
like what wait what the [ __ ] you what
did you just write down what was that no
what was that sorry I wasn&#39;t the [ __ ]
quarterback okay it doesn&#39;t mean you got
to write in your little book did you
write Antonio did you write that cuz I
said it [ __ ] five times did you write
that in your little [ __ ] book huh
yeah hi my name is
Logan not a great start log sorry logs
not a hot start dude did you also
duplicate your name slide five times
okay some technical nice this is a
drawing that I drew I am a twitch
streamer and also I&#39;m in corporate
marketing whatever that means lastly I
am a very big meme enjoyer so these are
some memes that I no no I told a girl to
text me when she got home she must be
homeless it&#39;s kind of
funny definitely don&#39;t say meme enjoyer
though for sure don&#39;t say that currently
enjoy hope uh you also
[Laughter]
enjoy about me uh I am actually 51%
confirmed Asian genetics uh with an
average statistic of 47.9% oh [ __ ]
that&#39;d be so funny ah [ __ ] he had the
opportunity to do the funniest thing
about me what if it was just about me
and then it&#39;s just like stats about
humans like I thought he was going to be
like I&#39;m 60% water as it turns out as
probably most of you in here are fun
fact about me my blood makes up about 8%
of my body
weight Isn&#39;t that cool next if you laid
my intestines out and to end they&#39;d be
about 4 miles
long European genetics uh from my
experience I have amass a total of 6t
and 1 in of height uh throughout my
years of growth of course she of course
you&#39;re writing that down of course wow
circled I have a great relationship with
management my mom I like to code I&#39;m
proficient in many languages including
English and memes as I am an avid
consumer of them hi I&#39;m David and I&#39;m a
software developer for work but my real
passion is playing tennis let&#39;s go David
semi unprofessional okay okay I like
these dudes trying to be funny in here
it&#39;s like how do I show her I&#39;m like an
alpha but still like be you know kind of
[ __ ] self-deprecating about it you
know like I [ __ ] rock at tennis but
I&#39;m not that good you know I&#39;m semi
unprofessional I&#39;ll kick you your ass
though and most dude&#39;s asses especially
if they [ __ ] like you know try to
insult you or whatever like I&#39;ll come to
your defense but like and like a cool
way I play like pretty much every day
and I do some coaching on the side as
well um and I also really like traveling
so I travel a lot and I&#39;m always looking
for a new experiences and so a little
about me I originally am from she&#39;s just
writing shorta I grew up in Minnesota
and I lived there most of my life and I
also bring additional skills to the
table I can do an oil change or rotate
your tires or recharge your AC in your
car I like to hear that one and I
learned all that on YouTube cuz I&#39;m good
at following directions so here are a
few of my hobbies and interests I play a
lot of tennis and I&#39;m also like really
into the outdoors and you know music is
a really important part of my life so I
really like going to concerts or music
festivals and hopefully I could do some
of those things with
you that was that was wholesome as [ __ ]
man I kept waiting for a little bit of
meat for me to bite on to you know but
you got nothing I like music I like
concerts I&#39;m from Minnesota um I&#39;m good
at being I&#39;m good at taking orders um so
boss me around if you want um like
snowboarding and uh just really hope to
do those things with you so um I do like
the shirt color thank you just ain&#39;t
going to cap that&#39;s real nice um so I
work in sales but my biggest passions
are acting and music I do sometimes
impersonation sometimes so those are
really really fun um so you got to do
one you got you know what you&#39;re doing
when you say that you know what you&#39;re
doing throw one of your throw one of
your favorites at me we&#39;ll see if I can
do it um I love playing it that was an
invitation what are you doing that was
crowd interaction amazing I like this
guy although he should have been like
give me one who in the audience wants to
give me one you know instead he was like
he kind of assumed that she would do it
so maybe you know one day give me your
you know what someone you want me to do
impression of maybe maybe I got it
so okay next slide unless anyone has
anything to say no okay okay cool did I
hear Quinton Tarantino or no
right okay F cool next SL did I hear
Steve bshi somebody no okay next slide
let&#39;s go on next slide basketball I can
also cook a lot of food so mama had us
in the kitchen that&#39;s what happens when
you have a Caribbean mom so she always
made sure we were going to be able to
take care of those things how I would
describe myself I would say I&#39;m very
very easygoing I like to have a good
time I go with the flow of um [ __ ]
okay graphic designer damn all right
Johnny I this looks beautiful though
look at this people&#39;s personalities and
last but not not least looks like a
ransom note a little bit actually looks
a little threaten hey what it do
handsome you know what I&#39;m
saying all right hey everybody hi let&#39;s
all right
yakie let&#39;s go yakie I&#39;m rooting for you
dude I just like I like that he kind of
I don&#39;t know I feel like all the rest of
the guys kind of had like a sort of like
I don&#39;t know cool sort of like
alternative swag and then I feel like he
just came up like he
came like he came just straight from his
you know I don&#39;t know Finance job or
something like hi I&#39;m yakie cool I
actually did an Excel spreadsheet um
instead of a PowerPoint sorry I
misunderstood the the uh the the
instructions and I&#39;m just generally I&#39;m
just stronger with Excel you&#39;re probably
wondering who is he sure am ah and
there&#39;s a handsome boy my occupation I&#39;m
an actor comedian musician writer and
educator okay all right Miss sorry I
judge the book by its cover maybe it&#39;s
the sweater which is a cool sweater but
you know I don&#39;t know it&#39;s very sweatery
and I&#39;m frequently tired but good at
functioning as a tired person let&#39;s
start with the obvious things like most
people I like movies music books art and
good food I&#39;m really into comedy stuff
and I also like making music um and I
also like
cats bro are we the same
person oh my sparkling personality
here&#39;s some photos of me being sparkling
[Music]
wow who are you picking comment below
all right you know what [ __ ] it Joseph
comment so I put together some green
flag flag and red flags that I
personally look for okay I&#39;m looking for
someone that&#39;s reliable someone that has
a good relationship with their parents
and or siblings uh someone that&#39;s not
easily stressed someone who can kind of
keep it together red flags that I run
from uh someone that&#39;s always late it&#39;s
okay to be a little late I&#39;ll be on CPT
myself but not like not every every time
everywhere we go and then also if you
cheated in all of your relationships
kind of a red
flag in all of them 100% of them 85% I
I&#39;m cool with that you know I I can deal
with with that that&#39;s no problem I&#39;m I&#39;m
willing to be that 15% and then also no
relationship with parents what if she&#39;s
orphan dude everything that um I&#39;m a
pretty open person so I&#39;m looking for
someone who&#39;s not afraid to talk about
uh what they&#39;re feeling in that given
moment um and if they party more than
they work I think it&#39;s okay to party
hard but I think you should also work
hard as well and I think that&#39;s the end
of my
presentation this is a solid
presentation it was a solid presentation
you made you made a great case for
yourself and um I I&#39;d say you&#39;re in the
running also I created a graph to show
you uh what it would look like if you
spent time with me so as we can see fun
is directly correlated to time spent
with me down here less time more time
more fun I also added some visuals here
so you can enjoy and understand the
graphs a little bit better as we can see
emojis look at that emojis cuz I&#39;m a I&#39;m
not like the other guys all right I
don&#39;t just when I convey messages I like
to do with little pictures not just
boring words he went like the quirky
route you know which is working she&#39;s
laughing and I think that&#39;s probably
that&#39;s probably winning them some points
here laughter is definitely important
but it&#39;s some of this a little cheesy
and I added some emojis and then look
what the third layer is I added some
memes on top of that yeah you can pretty
much tell that a date with me is going
to be like the most fun thing in the
entire
world okay unless you don&#39;t want that
see you&#39;ll be crying non stop less time
always crying up there we have a heart
eyes a rocket ship and an infinity
symbol which means you&#39;ll have heart
eyes to infinity and beyond I like to
travel and then
like heart eyes to infinity and beyond
and then he clicks it again like an
eggplant and a squirt shows up and oops
oh [ __ ] um H man I put that in as a joke
I left that in though that&#39;s Fu uh a
picture over there is when I went to on
a solo trip to Korea um I like long
walks to the fridge I eat everything
I&#39;ve tried everything
once long walks to the fridge come on I
want to try everything once uh my mom
thinks I&#39;m at least a four out
10 uh it ain&#39;t much but it&#39;s honest work
one of the memes I enjoy green flag some
of the green and red flags that I
have or I can cook but I mainly cook
chicken I&#39;m a great listener but I also
she&#39;s cheesing look at that she is
cheesing she&#39;s loving him she&#39;s writing
down what is she writing little hearts
or around his name play too many video
games I&#39;m independent but I can&#39;t watch
any scary
movies I&#39;ve amassed a total amount of
2,000 to 2,000 hours in rocket League
pretty cool if I say so myself I can act
maybe leave that one off maybe leave
that one off bro predict any number
you&#39;re guessing between 1 and
20 is it
16 so
close anyways that&#39;s the end of my slide
thank you guys so much hope you enjoyed
personally not my favorite but who knows
she seemed to be enjoying it so I feel
like you&#39;re pretty you&#39;re pretty high up
there right now photo of uh me and two
my best friends just the
whome the most non-threatening guy ever
a picture of me and my best friends and
just hanging out and this is actually us
uh we were exploring a Cave System
actually right underneath one of the
dorms of my college
who holy [ __ ] and he&#39;s adventurous and
so green flags I look for in a partner
you know I really like uh girls that are
practical ambitious good sense of humor
is really important um adventurous like
willing to try new things I really look
for Good Chemistry so like if we can
talk and we just talk for hours and we
just never run out of things to talk
about um and also nice teeth because a
good smile I think really gets me and
you know red flags for me is like not
being what that always throws me off the
editing that editing is like the last
dude&#39;s presentation you know what I mean
being uncaring and that could be to me
or to others or being a picky eater cuz
I I really like trying new foods and so
here&#39;s what I bring to the table so I&#39;m
a hopeless romantic emphasis on hopeless
I&#39;m a good listener I&#39;ll always validate
your feelings and my arms are
disproportionately long so I give really
good hugs I just want to be you know one
of the couples that other people look at
and go that could be us David that&#39;s so
[Applause]
cute this is the nicest guy in the
entire world I think it might be I don&#39;t
I think this guy has a bad bone in his
body look at that all the dudes are like
I&#39;d [ __ ] date this guy wow let me
know if she doesn&#39;t work out
dude for me I&#39;ve only been in four
relationships but I would say for me
every single person that I have dated
they brought something to the table that
makes me who I am these are the flags we
going to talk about so green flags for
me I love when people are honest even if
it even if it hurts right like we should
tell the truth passionate loves sports
is creative has a good taste in movies
and music um you know down to earth and
is really competitive and then I would
say red flags for me are if you&#39;re just
super self-absorbed you don&#39;t have any
drive like you&#39;re not going for anything
um don&#39;t like to work out that green
flags my green flags are if they&#39;re
perfect and then my red flags are if
they&#39;re a murderer can&#39;t be a serial
killer no thank you I don&#39;t want any
part of that that&#39;s a red flag in my
book green flags Perfection if they&#39;re
perfect then I&#39;m down I love to work out
out um someone that&#39;s just very
judgmental that&#39;s not open to like
hearing people&#39;s stories and having
empathy and then someone that&#39;s just
like rude to people that&#39;s just not
really a Vibe for me just bringing
things who is looking for someone that
is rude to people who is looking for
that do people look for that I don&#39;t
think so oh my God I love when people
treat waiters like [ __ ] I love that
service people [ __ ] scum right I love
when people recognize that and treat
them as such so hot bringing things to a
wrap up why I think I&#39;m your guy is
because number one I&#39;m fun I&#39;m
intelligent I&#39;m a natural born leader
I&#39;m energetic sweet when I want to be
spicy when I have to be and encouraging
sweet when I want to be spicy when I
have to be that&#39;s a bar you know what
that spells
finesse sick so in case you saw that you
know what I&#39;m saying so here&#39;s the deal
with me without me with me without with
me without me with me without me
wow so this is the reasons why you
should pick me this song is actually
coming out so we can if you end up
coming on a date with me or whatever we
can listen to this together is this your
song
Yes wait
no no you you&#39;re killing it dude you
were killing it a man what a horrible
pitch so if you went on a dat we could
potentially listen to this song My
unreleased song together I could sit
there and watch you listen to it and
just like kind of read your face and you
have to like pretend like it&#39;s good
thoughts thank you very much appreciate
[Applause]
you that just shouldn&#39;t be like you just
like if there&#39;s not like social proof
that your music is good I mean I you
know I should be one to [ __ ] talk but
I make one [ __ ] thing and I&#39;m like
put it on on Soundcloud right away but
if there&#39;s no like social proof that
people really really enjoy your music
then this is like a fifth date thing you
know where you&#39;re like hey I just work
I&#39;ve been working on something could I
show you and just get your opinion it&#39;s
not like a and you might be the lucky
lady that gets to listen to this
unreleased song by me with me if you
play your cards right empathetic I&#39;m
patient and I&#39;m considerate I&#39;m a good
planner but I&#39;m also adaptable
spontaneous and go with the flow and I&#39;m
not the jealous type I&#39;m pretty secure
so that&#39;s I think a good selling point
we love a secure man we love
that uh I&#39;m also organized responsible
but I&#39;m also fun and sociable um and I
prioritize Mak
connections some of this I just lifted
from my nectar love
print the [ __ ] is that what the [ __ ] is
nectar love print I&#39;m emotionally
intelligent and fairly self-aware and uh
My Love Languages include physical touch
and quality time and also sometimes acts
of service depending on the relationship
Dynamic okay here&#39;s just some fun bonus
info uh here&#39;s me hanging out with
friends just being very normal and
fitting in um I&#39;m a bit of that guy
knows hanging out with friends he&#39;s like
did you not see the first picture of my
[ __ ] slideshow that was me hanging
out with my best friends by the way
exploring a Cave System underneath our
dorm a nerd and I&#39;m a big proponent of
therapy so I like therapy I feel like
it&#39;s good to be working on
ourselves uh I&#39;m Jewish uh and I live
alone I have no roommates which I feel
like is another huge selling point it is
thank you and then I&#39;ll just end boy I
really was paraphrasing my next
here so here&#39;s just a big block of text
and on a very flattering photo of myself
as a
baby so there we go that&#39;s
[Applause]
it not the strongest I would say I don&#39;t
think he made the strongest impression
he seems like a nice guy but just not
this you know I don&#39;t know questions
about some things you said have you ever
cheated in a relation do you want the
truth or you want a li I want the truth
you can&#39;t handle the truth
stop doing that uh I do not I&#39;ve cheated
in the past when I was younger and more
immature uh I think you can like grow
and mature as a person so I feel like
I&#39;ve done that I appreciate that Honesty
you said you can cook I can but I&#39;m
pescatarian so I don&#39;t eat any chicken
okay so then I&#39;m thinking we can have
some class did I say chicken a [ __ ] I&#39;m
meant chicken of the Seas
tuna uh quinoa oven baked salmon uh
maybe some either you know normal
vegetables as broccoli asparagus or
baked kale with some lemon zest on top
okay I&#39;ll take it you mentioned music
and I was interested what kind of music
you&#39;re into so I what&#39;s he going to say
what the [ __ ] is he going to say he&#39;s
going to say everything he&#39;s going to
say I like all music I&#39;m not genre
dependent or he&#39;s going to say like soft
Electronica listen to a lot of like
Indie Indie yeah that makes sense that
was my third guess um and so um I really
like glass animals um before they were
big really something that you said was
that you had your four relationships and
I want to know what you think they would
say about you I think that they would
definitely say that I&#39;m very attentive
that I&#39;m somebody that is always seeking
and striving to be better in
relationship to both of us as that&#39;s a
funny answer first of all I didn&#39;t even
think of that answer that&#39;s like that&#39;s
so like I think that they would say that
I I work I just work too damn hard you
know make too much money I think they
would they got frustrated just how much
how much attention I was paying to them
how much love I was showing them and how
much money I made and how much I cooked
for them I just that&#39;s what they said
you know what I actually wrote this song
about exactly that and let me play that
for you this one&#39;s unreleased as well
okay I like that do you do like standup
comedy improv like what do you into all
the above I&#39;ve done both for a number of
years yeah sick his presentation was
very like stand deppy wasn&#39;t it I&#39;m
actually Jewish um like everything had
that like sort of like Cadence and like
intonation is that the word I&#39;m caring
but uh I&#39;m also attentive so much thank
you you guys made this very hard uh I
wasn&#39;t expecting it to be so hard and
all right favorite right now um you know
I was liking Joseph&#39;s presentation but
the music thing just that that uh I
don&#39;t know that took him down a couple
pigs in my in my eyes I don&#39;t know why
you know so now I&#39;m kind of thinking
nice guy although Nice Guy&#39;s always
finished last so he&#39;s not going to win
we know that I&#39;m I&#39;m surprised by a lot
of these things but I think the person
that I&#39;m going to eliminate I&#39;m
eliminating them
because they said something that is
actually one of my red
flags and so unfortunately although I
love the honesty I&#39;m going to have to
eliminate
Antonio oh I mean we knew he was done
from the moment he said he&#39;s too short
to be a quarterback we knew he was done
that was it that was it he dug his own
grave there there God I&#39;m so sorry not
the
chair I don&#39;t necessarily think once a
cheater always a cheater but I don&#39;t
even want to put myself in that type of
position so it was just an immediate X
for me hi again I&#39;m Logan uh and this is
my idea of the perfect date oh we got
more presentation I thought they were
done okay first date ideas okay so short
and sweet I really like he&#39;s like okay
First Date Presentation here uh okay
first slide I think that would be great
just eggplant squirt Emoji oh [ __ ] why
do I [ __ ] sorry I ah sorry mini golf
I think this would be the absolute
perfect date it&#39;s really relaxed and
stressfree it&#39;s also a lot of time to
talk so it&#39;s a great time where I can
get to know you we can talk about things
that we are interested in you know get
to know each other while we&#39;re putting
through the green I can&#39;t name a single
mini golf place in La do they exist here
I don&#39;t know I don&#39;t think so I think
Mini golf dates just happen in movies I
don&#39;t think people actually do that do
they let me know am I just like in the
little La bubble or something added a
fun little animation of what it would
look like if we play mini
golf it was a little frowny face cuz you
missed do I like mini golf oh
no this is a preview of what it looked
like to have dinner with oh my God
sweetheart look at this look at this
[ __ ] meal too do you think you made
all this probably and you said you&#39;re
pescatarian mhm uh do you like sushi I
love love that&#39;s great cuz I am obsessed
and I really like trying new things so I
was thinking that we could and I found a
some interesting Sushi making classes in
downtown and I was thinking we could go
to a class together and we could learn
to make sushi just get to learn to make
succulent sushi rice you really had to
put succulent in there dude you couldn&#39;t
have thought of any other word but
succulent in your presentation just get
to feel each other out a little bit also
dinner&#39;s built in so we can eat we can
eat what we made afterwards amazing um
after that we could take a drive out to
to Santa Monica Pier at night and we
could you know watch the sunset over the
beach I don&#39;t know about that you got
all of LA to do stuff and you&#39;re going
to pick the most the number one most
touristy thing in LA to do I don&#39;t know
about that I think the waves are
actually better when you&#39;re watching
them at night cuz it really feels like
you&#39;re in a movie and if there&#39;s one
thing that I try to do is I try to live
my life like I&#39;m in a future
film holy
[ __ ] wait what the [ __ ] did he just drop
my life as a movie at the end of oh my
god dude that was so out of character
for that that was so out of character
for him and if there&#39;s one thing that I
try to do is I try to live my life like
I&#39;m in a future
film D my friends and I always say that
[ __ ] Ah that&#39;s so funny people always
say my life a movie last night was a
movie so like I feel like it&#39;s funny to
try and find like different forms of
that you know I mean this isn&#39;t [ __ ]
new if it&#39;s one thing I try to do is try
to live my life like I&#39;m in a feature
film that&#39;s some sauce right there dude
and if it&#39;s one thing I try to do
is I try to live like I&#39;m in a clation
movie so so here we have um a kitchen so
what I did with this whole picture is is
like a kind of variety of different
experiences right so you can do an at
home type of a date situation I love to
cook and you said you&#39;re a prescatarian
so one of my favorite dishes to make is
like a salmon pasta dish but in my head
I&#39;m thinking wait a minute we could do
this together so it&#39; be a process where
we&#39;re working together almost a little
competition but a whole lot a character
and then we get to try the the outcome I
know it&#39;s delicious but you know you&#39;re
going to have to find out um I&#39;m a
really really big fan of going to comedy
shows like comedy shows are really
really great because you know we can
both sit there I love the guy&#39;s
reactions they&#39;re like H [ __ ] [ __ ] I
should have said that [ __ ] we can laugh
um and then and then finally as the
final Act you&#39;re going to watch me
perform my brand new unreleased song
after something is over just go and and
sit down somewhere really really nice or
go for a walk head to the beach over
here all right I would like to go on
David&#39;s date so if you if you could take
me that would be great um but in Li of
that here&#39;s another option this is
called this could be for you wow uh and
I went with a weird theme which is uh
stuff stuff based around Vermont Avenue
um I don&#39;t know why but I thought uh and
you know remember nothing set in stone
here thank you uh location one Griffith
Park Vermont entrance keepy it on theme
activity a little hike and then walk
around the observatory and admire the
view possibly at Sunset if I time it
right H look at that breathtaking so
here&#39;s some options a uh right down the
street is lots of cool artsy bookstores
and music shops and other like vintage
stores um or if you go a little further
down the street there&#39;s a family arcade
which is I think fun and a little
different oh yeah arcade now we&#39;re
talking little dve Busters ideal date
that&#39;s perfect or somebody already said
this but if you go even further down
Vermont Avenue oh my gosh there&#39;s
bowling uh and then finally because at
this point I&#39;m sure we&#39;ve worked up a
big appetite we should have dinner and
there&#39;s so many good neighborhoods right
there that have delicious food and this
is pictures of food I also like sushi
and tacos and burgers and ramen and all
kinds of stuff and we&#39;ll be we&#39;ll be so
hungry at that point so that&#39;s it I
really loved all of these pitches they
were all great and those were great but
I mean I feel like I feel like they were
just trying to describe like an ideal
date we can make food together or we
take Sushi classes you know I wish one
dude was like you know we&#39;re going to
[ __ ] get hammered probably yeah
probably take you to a rave just
something to that&#39;s like just doesn&#39;t
fit at all in this Warehouse Rave had an
element about it that I would like
whether that&#39;s like having some time to
talk with one another or the actual
activity that we&#39;re doing I think I&#39;m
going to have to eliminate this person
because like I said I just don&#39;t know
about she&#39;s getting rid of uh white boy
sweating on a first date if it&#39;s really
hot and doing a big hike so I&#39;m so sorry
but I&#39;m going to have to eliminate Yaky
that&#39;s okay thank you later Yaky nice
work dude nice work you did the best you
could he did a great job he did a great
job he&#39;s a Charming guy
you I don&#39;t know if we should have
clapped for that I think that a girl
that would be really good for him she&#39;s
going to be a little bit quirkier than I
am you know I want him to have the best
and I just don&#39;t think for him it&#39;s me
okay so when I first got here I was
really nervous and when you guys were
doing your presentations and opening up
to me who&#39;s she going to pick you think
it&#39;s going to be the meme guy it&#39;s not
going to be the nice guy because nice
guys come last even though his life is
literally a feature film even though
every day in his life is like the
premiere of a Hollywood movie yeah my
life is kind of a Marvel movie um I
think it might be Joseph made me feel
really open and really receptive and one
of you guys I feel like I just loved
their energy and their Vibe and their
authenticity and I want to pick this
person because I feel like I have a lot
of things in common with them and I
don&#39;t know I think that they&#39;re really
great and they&#39;re cute and they seem fun
so I&#39;m going to pick
David uh
what what all right maybe his [ __ ]
life is a movie damn that&#39;s a movie
thing that just happened that would
happen in a [ __ ] movie and it just
happened so maybe my my boy&#39;s life is a
freaking indie film perhaps uh or in
this case a romcom
damn thank you thank you they just start
making out it&#39;s like whoa this dude&#39;s
life is a [ __ ]
movie oh
yeah don&#39;t forget your
chairs I&#39;m really excited for hopefully
our Sushi date that comes to fruition I
really like the how you have things in
common with me I I didn&#39;t really list
that many uh things I like how you have
things in common with me
Riz RZ about me so I&#39;m really glad that
some of those things we already have in
common well I think like the fact that
you&#39;re hopeless romantic I I think that
that really speaks to me like I like
someone who&#39;s going to be like soft and
like affectionate and kind and sweet she
just calls you soft he&#39;s like all right
should we go suck down some succul and
Sushi or what&#39;s up oh that was fun that
was a great [ __ ] video I had a blast
hope you enjoyed that uh click like if
you did and uh thank you so much I&#39;ll
see you next time bye we up too
late it&#39;s like we&#39;ll never stop it
said you bring a friend I said okay got
it