you need a system that's it I would want
to code every day I even had the time to
but I would get so anxious from looking
at all the projects or challenges I
could do that I would just give up and
start wasting time that was until I
built the system and I call it the
coding menu it's a list of all the
coding I can do by time and energy
levels so for example if I only had an
appetite to code 30 minutes for the day
I can just write a small project like a
weight converter or try a super easy
coding challenge like twosome and even
if my project doesn't work or my
Challenge Fails I can always do it again
tomorrow but what if I don't want to do
that or if I get bored in that case I
had a list blocked by time and options
like a menu once I had this list even if
I was tired and I could only code for
just 30 minutes having an exact plan for
my time got me coding almost naturally
to the point where days I couldn't
program felt weird and having a menu or
a plan on what I should do took all the
thinking away so I could just get to
work whenever I wanted and seeing my
GitHub get greener is almost magical but
wait a minute why should I even do this
coding is a skill and you can only
improve if you practice your craft every
day you can't expect to improve from day
one but once you've programmed for
enough time you'll look back on your
code and find out where you want to
improve progress only happens in small
incremental chunks you can't become a
master overnight you just have to put
your head down and keep trying and one
day you'll see how far you've come thank
you for your time I am big box